Guide to the Rice University Dean of Undergraduates records, 1965-2004 UA 144
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series VII: Matt Taylor, Associate Dean of Undergraduates 1950-2009
  - Quality Enhancement Program (QEP): Boyer Center Conference, 2005-2006 (Box 30, Folder 49)
  - NCAA Handbook, 2007-2009 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - NCAA Division I-A Certification Self-Study Report, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - NCAA Site Visit, 2008 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - NCAA Academic Support Services/2.2 Review, 2008 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Student Interest Survey Guide, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - NCAA Student Handbook, 2007-2008 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - NCAA Annual Reports, 2005-2007 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - NCAA 2.1 Revision/Call Back, 2008 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - NCAA 3.2 Documents, 2003-2008 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - NCAA Student Forums, 2008 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - NCAA/Coaches IV's, 2008 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - NCAA/Coaches Survey, 2008 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - NCAA 3 Yr Stats, 2007-2008 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Common Data Set, 2007-2008 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Gruber Committee: Report of the Committee on Masters and Resident Associates, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Gruber Committee:, 2005-2006 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Gruber Committee: Masters'/RA Committee, 1986, 2005-2006 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Gruber Committee: Residential College Systems, 2004-2005 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - 50th Anniversary: Photo Display and Outtakes, 1998-2007 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - 50th Anniversary: 40th College Anniversary Alumni/Student Survey, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - 50th Anniversary: Panels, 2006-2007 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - 50th Anniversary: 50th Anniversary of the College System, 2006-2007 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - The Rice College System: Student Housing History, 1956-2007 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - The Rice College System: Early Policies, 1962-1973 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - The Rice College System: Additions and Coed Transition, 1957, 1970-1998 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - The Rice College System: 40th Anniversary, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - The Rice College System: Baker College, 1960-1977 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - The Rice College System: Will Rice College, 1971-1996 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - The Rice College System: Wiess College and Water/O-Week Controversy, 1950-1999 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - The Rice College System: W.V. Houston, 1954-1958 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - The Rice College System: Taylor Notes, 1987, 2007 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Woodson Documents on History of the College System, 1957-1998 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Report on the Committee on Student Housing, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Academic Affairs Committee Self-Study Report, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS) Accreditation, 2004-2005 (Box 31, Folder 35)